weathertech.com 2016-11-05

# Privacy Policy | Privacy Policy | WeatherTech.com

### WEATHERTECH DIRECT, LLC PRIVACY POLICY

We value you as a customer and take your privacy seriously and we want you to know how we collect, use, share and protect your information.

This Privacy Policy tells you:

    \- What information we collect

    \- How we use that information

    \- How we may share that information

    \- Your choices regarding your personal information

This Privacy Policy applies to [www.weathertech.com](http://www.weathertech.com/), WeatherTech Direct, LLC and any of its affiliated entities ("WeatherTech Direct, LLC") and information or pages found therein. Our Conditions and Terms of Use govern this Privacy Policy. To the extent there is a conflict between the terms of this Privacy Policy and the Conditions and Terms of Use, the Conditions and Terms of Use shall govern.

**If you visit or shop at WeatherTech.com,** _you accept and agree to be bound_ by our Conditions and Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy. Please read them carefully. If you do not agree, please do not visit or use this site. 

### INFORMATION WE COLLECT

We collect customer information in an effort to improve your shopping experience and to communicate with you about our products, services, contests, and promotions, and that we believe is necessary to administer our business. WeatherTech Direct, LLC recognizes that it must maintain and use customer information responsibly. We collect information such as your name, email address, mailing address, and phone and credit card numbers that you provide when you begin the checkout process by entering your email address, place an order, join our mailing list, register with us or participate in a contest, promotion or survey. We also may collect information that we deem necessary to maintain and administer your account with WeatherTech Direct, LLC. We also maintain a record of your product interests and your purchases online or in our retail store location. We may also collect information you give us about other people, such as the name and address of a gift recipient, or the name and contact info of a third party to receive any of our products or services. We may also collect information we receive about you from other sources, including third parties that help us update, expand and analyze our records and identify new customers.

### AGGREGATE AND ANONYMOUS DATA

Aggregate and anonymous data are information collected automatically through the operation of weathertech.com. ("AA Data") We may collect usage data (such as which website pages you visit with us and in what sequence) through the use of various technologies. For example, we may collect IP addresses from individuals who visit the website. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you’re surfing the Internet. Internet servers, the computers that "serve up" web pages, automatically identify your computer by its IP address. We do not link IP addresses to any Personal Information, so although your session may be logged, you will remain anonymous to us and our website. We may also collect password information from you when you log in, as well as computer and connection information such as browser type or version. During some visits, we may use software tools, such as Javascript, to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, time spent on certain pages, page interaction information, and methods used to browse away from the page.

### USE OF COOKIES AND SIMILAR TECHNOLOGIES

Like many websites, we use "cookies" or other similar technologies to collect AA Data. A cookie is a small data file that writes to your hard drive for record keeping purposes when you visit the website. Cookies allow the website to measure traffic activity on the website and to improve your user experience, for example, by remembering your passwords and viewing preferences, allowing you to visit restricted portions of the site, and tracking the progress and number of entries in activities that require registration or entry, such as sweepstakes, promotions, sales and contests. Similarly, if you have asked us to send you information about upcoming products and promotions, using cookies we collect information about which website pages you have visited and in what order ("Clickstream Data") that may allow us to narrow or limit the materials provided to you based on your prior online activities or preferences. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can set your browser to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent, but it is possible that some parts of the website will not function properly if you do so. In addition, we may use a service that collects data remotely by using so-called "pixel tags" "web beacons" clear GIFs" or similar means (collectively "Pixel Tags") embedded in the website’s content. A Pixel Tag is an electronic image, often a single pixel (1 x 1) that is ordinarily not visible to website visitors and may be associated with cookies on the visitors’ hard drives. This information is anonymous data.

### HOW WE USE INFORMATION ABOUT YOU

We use customer personal information to provide accurate services and to advise our valued customers of promotions that may be of interest to them. WeatherTech Direct, LLC does not sell, rent or trade your personal information to third parties. We may share your information with third parties to perform services on our behalf such as: fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending WeatherTech Direct, LLC marketing materials, fulfilling subscription services, conducting research and analysis, handling and processing credit card payments. We may disclose your personal information to trusted third parties whom we engage to process your personal information for us. We may disclose personal information with other companies and organizations for fraud and credit risk purposes. We may disclose your personal information to third parties with regard to the analysis and support of your use of the website. We may be required to share personal information in response to a regulation, court order or subpoena or discovery request. We may also share information to respond to a government request or when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property or safety of WeatherTech Direct, LLC, our customers, or others; to prevent harm or loss; or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual unlawful activity.

We may also share personal information in the event of a corporate sale, merger, acquisition, dissolution or similar event. We may share personal information in connection with financial products or services related to our business such as private label credit cards. We also may share personal information in connection with co-branded products or service offerings. For example, if we were to offer a WeatherTech Direct, LLC credit card, during the application process we may share your personal information with our banking partners that issue any such card.

### THIRD-PARTY ADVERTISING AND LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES

WeatherTech.com may contain links to other sites or contain third-party advertising. These third parties’ websites and advertisers, or the internet advertising companies that work on their behalf, may use technology to send (or "serve") the advertisements that appear on our website directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They also automatically receive and record information from your computer and browser, including your cookie information. They may also use cookies, Javascript, Pixel Tags and other technologies to deliver advertisements, collect information about the effectiveness of their advertisements, and to collect anonymous information about your visits to the website, such as the number of times you have viewed an ad or to customize the advertising content you see (but not your name, address or other personal information). The third parties’ use of their own cookies is subject to their own privacy policies. For information about these specialized cookies and other technologies, and how to "opt out" of information collection by these companies, we suggest you visit http://doubleclick.net/privacy_policy or http://networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp

Please be aware that this website may contain links to other sites that will not follow the same Privacy Policy as WeatherTech Direct, LLC. Clicking on an advertisement or on links or other elements on the website may take you to an entirely different website. These websites may send their own cookies to you and may collect data and make use of that data in ways that WeatherTech Direct, LLC would not. Once you have left this website, this Privacy Policy will no longer apply to any personal information or any other data collected from or provided by you. You should review the applicable privacy policy to determine how that other website will handle such data.

### DATA SECURITY DISCLAIMER

WeatherTech Direct, LLC takes reasonable security precautions to secure the personal information that you choose to provide us against loss, misuse, alteration or unauthorized access of such information. Unfortunately, no transmission of data over the Internet is guaranteed to be completely secure. It may be possible for third parties not under the control of WeatherTech Direct, LLC to intercept or access transmissions or private communications unlawfully. While we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any personal information you transmit to us. Any such transmission is done at your own risk. 

### CHILDREN’S PRIVACY

Consistent with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without prior verifiable parental consent. If we become aware that a user is under the age of 13 and has registered with WeatherTech Direct, LLC without prior verifiable parental consent, we will remove his or her personally identifiable information from our files. Please note that we nevertheless maintain a record of that person’s name and address in a "do not register" file to avoid subsequent registration by a child under the age of 13. By using this website you agree to respond truthfully and accurately about your age. Children under the age of 13 years are expressly prohibited from submitting or providing any personal information on the website.

### CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

Since January 1, 2005, under California law and if you are a resident of California, you may make a written request to WeatherTech Direct, LLC about how we have shared your personal information with select third parties for their direct marketing purposes. In response to your written request, WeatherTech Direct, LLC will identify the categories of information shared and will include a list of the third parties and affiliates with which it was shared, along with their names and address. Please submit a written request to the following address: 

Attn: Customer Service – California Privacy Policy

WeatherTech Direct, LLC

841 Remington Blvd.

Bolingbrook, IL 60440

Please allow thirty (30) days for a response.

### USER CONSENT

By providing any personal information to WeatherTech Direct, LLC, all users, including, without limitation, users in all foreign countries, fully understand and unambiguously consent to this Privacy Policy and to the transfer of such personal information across international borders in accordance with WeatherTech Direct, LLC standard operations, including the collection, storage and processing of such information in the United States of America.

### SAFE HARBOR

WeatherTech Direct, LLC complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland.  WeatherTech Direct, LLC has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement.  To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view WeatherTech Direct, LLC certification, please visit http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/

### **CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY**

WeatherTech Direct, LLC may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. Please review the Privacy Policy periodically. Each and any version and subsequent update of this Privacy Policy can also be printed for your records upon your review. You should periodically review this Privacy Policy because by agreeing to visit our website **_you agree to accept and be bound by any such changes_** that we make to the Privacy Policy. If you do not agree, then please do not visit the website. Except as otherwise mentioned herein, the Privacy Policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you on our website [www.weathertech.com](http://www.weathertech.com/).

### QUESTIONS ABOUT OUR PRIVACY POLICY AND YOUR CHOICES

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, or have any objections to this Privacy Policy, please contact us directly and direct your inquiries to our Customer Service Department at:

WeatherTech Direct, LLC

841 Remington Blvd.

Bolingbrook, IL 60440

(800) 441-6287

You may choose to stop receiving marketing or promotional emails, direct mail, phone and mobile marketing communications, update and correct your personal information, cancel your account or request that we no longer use your personal information to provide you services. To accomplish any of the requests, please contact us at the contact information given above and ask for our Customer Service department.
